

Blk-6 Lot-3 Isla Homeowners
Valenzuela City, 1444
2935042 | 09354635971
http://mlesterdampios.com
mlesterdampios@gmail.com
https://github.com/mlesterdampios
https://ph.linkedin.com/in/mark-lester-dampios-351986167

## MARK LESTER O. DAMPIOS, MIT

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I would like to enhance my skills to the industrial world of IT – such as to be entrusted with an opportunity on using my expertise in game development, website development, application designs and programming, that would help in my professional development and the growth of the company.

I would also like to make projects that would make a positive impact on the clients. Thus, I believe that happy clients are the key to success of a company and I want to be part of it.

#### **SKILLS**

- Responsible and hard-working
- Has a good leadership skills and a good team player
- Can work under pressure, efficiently and effectively
- Has a good oral communication skill

## **SKILL SET**

#### .NET DEVELOPMENT

- C#
- VB.NET
- MVC Framework

## **HYBRID APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT**

- NodeJS
- Cordova
- Ionic
- Angular

#### **WEB TOOLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- Javascript
- jQuery
- AJAX

### **GAME DEV TOOL**

Unity

### **DESKTOP DEVELOPMENT**

- C#
- Java

### **DATABASE TOOLS**

- MySQL
- SQL Server
- Firebase

### FRAMEWORKS AND OTHER TOOLS

- XAMPP
- Bootstrap
- Code Igniter
- Adobe Photoshop
- Wordpress

### **OPERATING SYSTEM**

- Windows
- Linux
- MAC OS

## **EDUCATION**

#### **ISLA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL**

SY. 2004 - 2010

#### POLO NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL

SY. 2010 - 2014

## PAMANTASAN NG LUNGSOD NG VALENZUELA

**Bachelor of Science in Information Technology** 

2014 - 2018

### **AMA UNIVERSITY**

**Master in Information Technology** 

2018 - Present

# WORK EXPERIENCES

## **Freelance**

Web, Mobile, Game Development

2015 - Current

### **Miyens Technologies**

https://www.miyens.com OJT Web Developer 2017 - 2018

### **NOVO Group of Companies**

IT Officer

2018 1st Quarter - 2018 2nd Quarter

## **Digital Genesis Lab**

https://digitalgenesislab.com/

Full-Time Developer / Freelancer

2018 3rd Quarter - Current

## SOME WORK SHOWCASE

### **My Online Portfolio**

http://mlesterdampios.com

### **Digital Genesis Lab**

Lead Developer / Project Manager http://www.dglabglobal.com/

#### **Intal Garments – E-commerce**

Lead Developer / Project Manager https://intalgarments.net/

## **Oohlalaa Hosiery – E-commerce**

Website Administrator – *Under Digital Genesis Lab* https://www.oohlalaahosiery.com/

### Frontman - Mobile App

Lead Developer / Project Manager – *Under Digital Genesis Lab* https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/frontman/id1449146104

## SEMINARS ATTENDED

## "SERVING JOYFULLY WITH PASSION AND PERFORMING WITH PRECISION IN THE HOSPITALITY INDUSTRY"

St. Mary's College of Meycauayan Meycauayan City, Bulacan

February 7, 2014

### "GLASS TECHNOLOGY"

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Valenzuela Poblacion II, Malinta, Valenzuela City

July 29, 2015

## "5TH INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY INNOVATIONS CONGRESS"

Unity3D, Character Animation, Windows Phone Programming and Technopreneurship

eGlobio Training Center Philippines

August 29, 2015

## "SHARE THE CLOUD"

Adamson University, Manila, Philippines

May 4, 2016

## "SAMSUNG REPAIR, BASIC CUSTOMER SERVICE AND INTRODUCTION TO SAMSUNG GALAXY VR"

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Valenzuela Poblacion II, Malinta, Valenzuela City

August 5, 2016

## "PHOTOSHOP USEFUL TECHNIQUES AND PRACTICES"

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Valenzuela Poblacion II, Malinta, Valenzuela City

August 5, 2016

## "IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT"

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Valenzuela Poblacion II, Malinta, Valenzuela City

September 3, 2016

## "AGILE/SCRUM IN A NUTSHELL"

Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Valenzuela Poblacion II, Malinta, Valenzuela City

September 3, 2016

## REFERENCES

## **Miyens Technologies (OJT)**

Website Designer 0908 195 3916

## **MS. ANNACHELLE BAYLON**

PLV Professor, IT Department 0916 670 4365